本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
是不是很棒啊
Isn't this nice?
全家在一起享受共度天伦之乐
We're all here together sharing family time.
(注：恶搞真人秀名人城堡)
妈妈别啰嗦了  "名宠城堡"已经开始了
Mom, please. "Celebrity pet castle" Is on.
没想到这节目可以召集那些名人家的宠物们
Who would have thought a show about celebrity pets.
让它们一起住在城堡里生活真是很妙的主意
Living together in a castle would be so great?
(注：美国名嘴和达人评委)
上星期啊  霍伊·曼德尔家的猫
Last week, howie mandel's cat.
吃掉了一条杰克·布莱克的孔雀鱼
Ate one of jack black's guppies.
真有意思
oh,cool
我本想我们可以关了电视
I was thinking we could turn the tv off.
等等  现在别关
Wait! Not now.
它们进入淘汰制了
They're starting with an elimination!
我去拿爆米花
I'll get the popcorn.
我现在可不想去当碧昂斯的仓鼠啊
I would not want to be beyonce's hamster right now.
咋啦
What?
老鼠啊  我看见一只老鼠
Mouse! I saw a mouse!
(注：北美的老鼠个头很小)
有这么大啊
It was like this big.
一定是你那花腔女高音尖叫把它吓跑了
And your high-pitched girl scream scared it away.
哈哈哈  快看看这个
Hey hey hey, look at this.
老鼠便便啊
Mouse droppings.
得奖了
Oh, bill.
这是一只落基山灰色属
That's a rocky mountain grey...
雌性
Female...
大概有孕在身
About to be a mother.
真恶心
That is just gross.
我可不要我家里有什么老鼠和老鼠崽
I do not want a mouse or mouse babies in this house.
哎呀  老鼠宝宝啊
Aw, mouse babies.
恶
Ew!
放心  没啥大不了的
Don't worry about it. It's not a problem.
你们不如都坐好了
You know what? Have a seat.
观摩一下灭害大师的专业表演吧
Watch a master exterminator in action.
要不我们还是回去看节目好了
Or we could get back to the show.
西蒙·考威尔的乌龟从壳里面探出头来了
Simon cowell's turtle is coming out of his shell.
真的哦
Oh!
生活搞得一团糟
Today's all burnt toast
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
Running late,and dad jokes
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
Has anybody seen my left shoe
我闭上双眼  咬口早餐
I close my eyes, take a bite
跳上车子  放声大笑
Grab a ride, laugh out loud
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
There it is up on the roof
■
翻译： 山鹰逢羽
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
I've been there, I've survived
所以听取我的建议
So just take my advice
■
后期： Johnny-Z  kenix
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, baby,
世界有很多疯狂无奈
Things are crazy
可是我知道你会有美好未来
But I know your future is bright
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
不要怀疑
There is no maybe
一切终会如你所愿
Eveything turns out all right
生活有悲有喜
Sure life is up and down
可是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
But trust me, it comes back all around
你会喜欢将来的你
You're gonna love who you turn out to be
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
查莉成长日记  第一季第十七集
Good Luck Charlie  S01E17  Kwikki Chick
真讨厌  这东西烦死个人
Ah, this thing is so frustrating.
老爸  可以给我买支新手机吗
Dad, can I get a new phone?
不行
Nope
爹地呀
Daddy.
能不能给人家买个新手机嘛  好不好嘛
Can I please get a new phone, please?
好啦  既然你都这么撒娇了
Well, since you put it like that...
还是不行
No.
可这旧电话根本不能用了
But this old phone is useless.
我又不能下载新程序  又不能更新状态
I can't download apps, I can't post status updates.
唯一的功能就是谈话
The only thing I can do on it is talk.
可现在根本没人继续用那种功能了
Nobody does that anymore.
好了  你想要个新手机是吧
Okay, you want a new phone?
给你吧  新手机哦
There you go. New phone.
无限通话时间  而且还会叽叽叫
Unlimited minutes. And it squeaks.
做的好  老爸
Good for you, dad.
对那公主说一次不吧
Tell the princess no for once.
说什么哪  我这个公主
Excuse me, but this princess.
比你梳头毛的时间都要少的多呢
Spends a lot less time on her hair than you do.
再说有你啥事儿啊
What's your problem, anyway?
要我说就是你一向是要风得风要雨得雨的
My problem is everything gets handed to you.
这大概是史上第一次没有照你的意愿得逞吧
This is like the first time in history something didn't go your way.
宝贝听好  要是你想要新手机  就去找个工作
Look, honey, if you want a phone, get a job.
我才15岁  能找到什么工作啊
I'm only 15. What kind of job could I get?
好吧  你知道不
All right, you know what?
这小区里有各种各样的狗
There's all sorts of dogs in the neighborhood.
你可以去帮别人遛狗
You could walk dogs.
不然...
Or…
不然就没有新手机
Or not get a new phone.
泰迪  工作不只是为了赚钱
Teddy, a job isn't just about money.
也是为了体现自我价值和尊严
It's also about self-worth and dignity.
哇哦
Wow.
好了  伙计们  我们俩要去上音乐课了
Okay, everybody, we are off to our music class.
你看上去真漂亮
You look so cute.
哎呀  查莉  有没听见你家姐夸你美啊
Aww, charlie, did you hear what your big sister said about you?
我是说你呢  妈妈
I was talking to you, mom.
你嘴真甜呢
Oh, you're so sweet.
不过我也不会给你新手机
And you're not getting a phone.
大家听着  炸鸡行业面临危机
Okay, people, the fried chicken business has taken a hit.
显然目前油炸食物有害于健康
Apparently fried is now bad for your health.
所以我们要设法增加营业额
So we need to think of ways of increasing our sales.
说说看吧  你说
Dazzle me! You.
不如我们在菜单上加上墨西哥卷吧
How about we introduce tacos to our menu?
太简单了  太没创意了  大家再多加油啊
Too easy, too expected. Push it, people.
给力啊  你说
Punch it! Yeah?
要不我们炸些别的便宜的肉食
How about we fry up other, cheaper kinds of meat.
跟顾客说是炸鸡  但其实不是鸡肉
And tell people it's chicken, only it's not chicken?
我们已经是那么做了  你刚才就吃了三个
We're already doing that. You had number three lately?
使劲想啊  你们这些拿最低工资的家伙
Work with me, minimum wagers.
必须给我想点招出来
Give me something!
你有啥主意  JP
What you got? J.P
我叫PJ
It's p.J.
随便吧  快说
Whatever. Go.
我们给这生意造一个脸面形象吧
Well, what if we give the business a face?
找一个咕唧鸡形象代言人
Someone who is kwikki chikki.
把她头像印在海报和纸袋还有全家桶上
Someone to put on posters and bags and buckets.
就像汉堡王鲍比一样
Like bobby burger.
我可喜欢汉堡王鲍比了
I like bobby burger.
他吃汉堡吃不停
He always eats the burgers.
对吧  我们就是少了这种人
See? That is what we're missing.
咱没有咕唧先生啊
We don't have a mr. Kwik!
咕唧先生  唔  说下去
Mr. Kwik? Mr. Kwik. Tell me more.
好哒  他应该是公司的员工
Well, he should be an employee.
要年轻帅气
Probably young, good looking,
健康活力
Healthy.
你是在说我吧
You're thinking me, right?
或是哪位年轻些
Or someone young,
帅气活力的
Good looking, healthy.
咕唧先生
Mr. Kwik.
这事明天再说
I'm going to sleep on it.
好了  干活吧  十点开门  表现积极点
All right, people, doors open in 10, so look lively.
哦  那是啥味儿啊
Oh, and what is that smell?
店里炸鸡的味道啊
That's our chicken.
是么
Ah
我干这行二十年了  一直都没习惯过
20 years in the business. You never get used to it.
你在干啥呢  老爸
What are you doing, dad?
我在用超猛的好料做这个捕鼠器
I am loading the mouse trap with a tasty little snack.
满载着花生酱和恐怖滋味啊
Of peanut butter and horror.
你还没抓到那老鼠啊
You haven't caught that thing yet?
孩子们  听爸爸教诲吧
Kids, let me explain something to you.
我现在可不只是抓老鼠那么简单
Now I'm not just a guy who catches things.
不用说啊
Clearly.
我也是专业的动物行为专家
I am also an expert in animal behavior.
今晚这只落基山小灰能吃的肚儿圆
Now the rocky mountain grey feeds at night.
明早上呢  这笼子里就有个老鼠住客了
So by tomorrow morning this trap. Is going to have a mouse in it.
亲爱的顾客们  这可是本店信誉保证
And that, my friend, is a guarantee.
百分百担保的
100%.
得有人给他泼泼冷水
Somebody needs to take him down a peg.
你要去给老爸捣乱吗
Are you gonna mess with dad?
我可是捣蛋大师盖比啊
I'm gabe. It's what I do.
(注：出自《鹅妈妈童谣》)
铜板就这么花掉了
That's the way the money goes
伙计  我的裤子也当给你啦
Pop!goes the weasel.
唱的好
Good job.
大家都很棒唷
Great job, everybody.
好啦  现在我们先休息一下
Okay, we're gonna take a little juice break,
之后我们就开始一起跳熊熊舞哦
Then we will come back for dance-a-lance-a-ling-long!
歇会
Oh.
你好  我是伊莲
I'm elaine, by the way.
认识你很高兴
Nice to meet you.
我是艾米  这是我女儿查莉
I'm amy, and this is my daughter charlie.
查理吗
Charlie?
(注：著名漫画人物)
查理·布朗的那个查理吗
Like, charlie brown?
不是啦  不是查理·布朗那个啦
No, not like charlie brown.
其实是查莉  是夏洛特的简称
Charlie, like, short for charlotte.
哦好吧  只要你们自己满意就好
Oh well, as long as it makes sense to you.
那这位是谁啊
And who is this?
她叫布兰妮哦
This is brittany.
对  就是你哦
Yes, you are.
哎呀  真是可爱呀
Oh, that's so adorable.
是吧
Yeah.
你给她取了个脑残明星的名字啊
You named her after a troubled pop star.
我注意到查莉拍手很来事的呀
I noticed charlie was very good at clapping.
当然啰  这只是她众多天赋之一啦
Oh yes, it's one of her many talents.
喔  我家布兰妮六个月就会拍手了  所以么
Aww, brittany was clapping at six months, so...
查莉会学动物叫
Charlie makes animal sounds.
查莉  母牛是怎么叫的啊
Charlie, what does a cow say?
汪
Woof.
真给力啊
Very impressive.
对了  正要告诉你
Oh, just so you know,
下堂课  我们会要每对母子一起唱首歌
Next class, we're asking every mom and child to perform a song together
哇  那应该很有意思啊
Oh, that sounds fun.
也想告诉你说  这个反正不是什么比赛
And just so you know, it's not a competition.
因为凭我音乐剧出身的背景
It wouldn't be fair
对其他人是很不公平的
with my musical theater background
我本来自百老汇
I was on broadway.
啊  那你现在沦落至此啊
Oh, and now you're here,
还真是昨日黄花咧
So we see how that turned out.
你咋啦
What happened to you?
我照你说的去当遛狗的
I took your suggestion and became a dog walker.
那条大麦町还有一条拉布拉多
A great dane and a larbadoodle.
发起疯来拖着我扑向一只小贵宾
Took turns dragging me through a puddle.
真是多谢你哦
So thanks.
不客气
You're welcome.
袋子里是啥
What's in the bag?
基本上都是大麦町拉的
Mostly great dane.
我能把这丢哪里去
Where should I put it?
垃圾桶啊
Trash can.
丢到达布尼太太的垃圾桶去
Mrs. Dabney's trash can.
嘿老爸  猜猜我干了啥
Hey, dad, guess what.
你总算按我要求洗了车啦
You washed the car like I asked?
你还真不擅长猜谜呢
You are really bad at guessing.
不是啦  我提了个工作建议  老板很赏识
No, I had an idea at work and my boss loved it.
干的不错啊
Hey, good for you.
对啊  少爷那时可牛了
Yeah, it was a great moment.
谁知道呢
And who knows?
也许咕唧先生就是伟大历程的起步啊
Mr. Kwik could be the start of something big.
太棒了
This is amazing.
自从你当了咕唧先生后  咱的生意一炮冲天
Ever since you became mr. Kwik business is booming.
我只想表达我的感谢  PJ
I just want to say, thank you, p.J.
我怎么可能带这么多钱回家啊
How am I gonna get all that money home?
你可以堆在后车厢里
You could put it in the trunk.
就是你那新车啊
Of your brand new car!
你能给我签名吗  咕唧先生
Can I have your autograph, mr. Kwik?
荣幸之至
Absolutely.
我这是签给哪位大驾啊
And who am I making this out to?
咕唧太太啰
Mrs. Kwik.
车不错
Nice car.
你倒是什么时候洗我那部先
When are you gonna wash mine?
老爸  别来搅和我的美梦
Dad, get out of my fantasy.
嘿嘿  小老鼠
Hello, little mouse.
咱们搭伙来给我爸捣蛋吧
Want to help me mess with dad?
爸
Dad!
抓到老鼠了吗
We have a mouse?
没  可饵食已经不见啦
No. But the bait is gone.
怎么会
What?
不会吧  这绝对不可能
Oh, come on. That's impossible.
一只小老鼠怎么可能做到的
How could a mouse do that?
我可不知道
I don't know.
不过看来它在逗你玩呢
It's almost like he's mocking you.
好啊  老鼠想要玩是吧
Okay, mouse wants to dance,
那咱就舍命陪君子
We're gonna dance.
真不晓得那些有聪明老爸的孩子平时有啥乐趣
I wonder what kids with smart dads do for fun.
小朋友们  我要进去一下下
Guys, I'm going inside for just a minute.
我离开的时候  可别乱吠
And while I'm gone no sniffing,
也不能乱咬乱拱哦
No biting and no scooching.
布鲁特斯  过来
And brutus, come here.
好兄弟记住  菲菲不是你的咬咬棒  好吗
Buddy, remember, fifi is not a chew toy, okay?
老板  你有没有考虑我那咕唧先生的主意
So, mitch, did you have a chance to think about my mr. Kwik idea?
我想过了  JP  不然我现在该叫你
Yes, I did, j.P. Or should I say...
咕唧先生
Mr. Kwik!
真的吗  让我做
Really? Me?
对  你就是咕唧炸鸡店的新形象了
Yup, you're the new face of kwikki chikki.
我看到你的锦绣将来了  前程一片美好啊
I see great things ahead for you. The future is bright.
这未来包括加薪吗
Does the future include a bump in pay?
那没门
No, it does not.
好吧  无所谓了
Well, doesn't matter.
作为咕唧先生已经是很高荣誉了
Being mr. Kwik is reward enough.
免费饮料有吗
Free soft drinks?
没门
No
不过你之前说的对  孩子
But you were right, kid.
咕唧炸鸡店的形象确实要年轻帅气
The face of kwikki chikki needs to be young,
健康活力
Healthy, good looking.
就像那位
Like that!
你是说我吧
You mean this?
不不不  你比不上她
Oh, no no no, this ain't that.
你还可以  可她是个尤物
This is good but that is great.
她不能是咕唧先生啊  她是个娘们
She can't be mr. Kwik. She's a girl.
那就不要咕唧先生了
Then forget about mr. Kwik.
她将成为我们的咕唧女郎
She'll be our kwikki chick.
你想当咕唧炸鸡的形象代言人吗
Are you ready to be the face of kwikki chikki?
我只是进来借厕所的
I just wanted to use the bathroom.
我真搞不懂你为啥生我的气啊
I just don't understand why you're mad at me.
我生气是因为你又来这套了
I'm mad at you because you did it again.
你就随便走进去  随心所欲就找到工作
You walked right in there and got the job handed to you.
而且是我的工作
My job.
我又不是故意的
I didn't do it on purpose.
你知道我当那咕唧先生当了多久吗
Do you know how long I was mr. Kwik?
三十七秒
37 seconds.
真是太短暂了
That's too quick.
那你希望我怎么做啊
What do you want me to do?
辞职  你反正已经有活干了
Quit. You already have a job.
遛狗吗  这活很恶心啊
Walking dogs? It's disgusting.
没有对你们不敬的意思  伙计们
No offense, guys.
PJ  我很遗憾你没得到那工作
P.J., I'm sorry you didn't get the job,
可我自己得到了就一点不遗憾
But I'm not sorry I did.
你当然没愧疚了  公主殿下
Of course you're not, princess.
别再那样叫我了
Stop calling me that!
那你就别再当公主了
Stop being that!
哎呀  布鲁特斯  怎么又来了  你不是吧
Oh, brutus, again? Really?
不过我还是会想你们大家的
I'm gonna miss you least of all.
夜视眼镜  装备完成
Night vision goggles... check.
你在干什么啊
What are you doing?
我在逮耗子啊
I'm catching a mouse.
还戴上红外线夜视眼镜  用得着吗
With night vision goggles? Really?
随便怎么说
Whatever it takes.
没人可以耍我鲍伯·邓肯大爷
Nobody makes a fool of bob duncan.
是没人  你自己独孤求败呢
No, he does that all by himself.
你  上楼睡觉去  别妨碍大师作法
Go back upstairs to bed and let the expert do his job.
去叫你妈来
Go get mommy.
咿呀咿呀哟
Ee-I-ee-I-oh!
- 祝你好运  - 领情
- Break a leg. - Uh-huh.
好了  宝宝  我们开始吧
Okay, here we go, baby.
一闪一闪小星星
Twinkle twinkle little star
满天都是小星星
How I wonder what you are
高高挂在天空中
Up above the world so high.
好象宝石放光明
Like a diamond in the sky.
别别别  查莉啊  拿好手电筒哦
No no no, charlie, grab the flashlight.
要对着妈妈照哦  照着妈妈
Put it back on mommy. Put it back on mommy.
小小蜘蛛爬出水管啰
The itsy-bitsy spider went up the water spout
下雨啦
Down came the rain
冲掉了小蜘蛛
And washed the spider out.
查莉宝贝  专心看妈妈好吗
Charlie honey, I need you focus.
妈妈就快精彩谢幕了哟
Mommy's about to do her big finish.
滴答  滴答  滴
Hickory dickory rock
老鼠爬上钟表上
The mouse ran up the clock
时针走到了十二点
The clock struck 12:00
接着我有别的话要说
then something else I said
滴答  滴答  滴
hickory dickory rock!
谢谢你们  丹佛市
Thank u, denver!
我们的咕唧女郎驾到啦
There's our kwikki chick!
好了  你要做的就是坐在这里
All right, so all you have to do is sit here,
给顾客签名并享用炸鸡
Sign autogphs and eat chicken.
我会做好的
I can do that.
JP  你给我过来
J.P., get over here.
我叫PJ
P.J.
错  从现在你的名字就是助理
Wrong. From now on your name is assistant.
是咕唧女郎的私人助理
As in assistant to the kwikki chick.
她需要任何东西  我说的是任何需要哦
If she needs anything, ani mean anything,
你都必须办到
You get it forer.
不用啦  麦切老板  PJ不用特地在旁等我
Now, mitch, p.J. Doesn't have to wait on me.
他当然要  因为这儿就是你的小小王国
Oh, yes he does. Because in our little kingdom.
您就是公主殿下
You're the princess.
这里有点热啊  你觉得热吗
It's warm in here. Are you warm?
我可不想看到你出汗  给她扇扇子
I do not want you perspiring. Fan her.
呃  麦切啊  他做的不称职
Um, mitch, he's not doing it right.
我想要你来扇
I want you to fan me.
其实我还有事
Oh, actually...
我是公主  给我扇  里奇
I'm the princess. Fan me, rich.
我叫麦切啦
It's mitch.
错  现在给我扇
Wrong! Now fan me.
觉得如何啊
How's this?
不许看着我
Don't look at me.
泰迪  你在干什么啊
Teddy, what are you doing?
闭嘴
Silence.
呃  你现在可以开始吃炸鸡了吧
Um, can you just eat the chicken now?
可以
Fine!
哇塞  这太吓人了
Mmm! Oh, that's awful!
她的意思是好吃的吓人啊
She means awful good.
呼
Ugh!
你们怎么吃得下这种垃圾
How can you people eat this stuff?
我看这店该叫做垃圾鸡才对
They should call this place icky chikki.
滚出去  你被炒了
Get out! You're fired!
哦  对了对了  仅供参考哦
Oh oh oh oh! And f.Y.I.
三号餐其实是马肉  老兄你懂的
The number three is horse meat, okay buddy?
马肉也美味呀
And delicious.
半价优惠哦
And half off.
好啊  老爸
Hey, dad.
你还穿着浴袍呢
You're still in your bathrobe.
你怎么不穿好衣服呢
Why aren't you dressed?
那又怎么样
What's the point?
你应该去上班了吧
Shouldn't you be at work?
没班好上了  我辞职了
There is no work. I quit my job.
等等  啥
Wait, what?!
如果我连一只小耗子都逮不到
If I can't catch a little mouse,
那就根本配不上灭害专家的称号
I don't deserve to call myself an exterminator.
对不起了
I'm sorry.
我是个废柴
I'm a failure.
不是啊  爸爸  你才不废呢
No, dad. You're not a failure.
你第一晚就逮到那只老鼠啦
You caught the mouse the first night.
是我在跟你捣蛋呢  我才对不起
I was pranking you. I'm so sorry.
我并不想弄的你要辞职的呀
I didn't mean for you to quit your job.
被我骗到了吧
I got ya!
咋回事
What?!
我逗你玩呢
I've been pranking you.
没门儿
No way.
有门儿
Yeah way.
你是怎么发现到的啊
How'd you figure it out?
我告诉过你  我是动物行为的专家
I told you, I'm an expert at animal behavior.
好吧  其实我看到你放跑了老鼠
All right, I saw you let the mouse go.
那上次你弄的那一堆老鼠夹子
So that thing you did with the mouse traps,
难道都是故意的么
You did that on purpose?
对  都是故意的
Yes, I did that on purpose.
不该你来跟我捣蛋啊  应该我捣蛋才对
You can't prank me, I prank you.
一直都是这样的啊
That's how it works.
不对哦
Oh no.
那是老一套啦
That's how it used to work.
换到别人立场的滋味如何啊
How does it feel to be on the other side?
我已经不知道自己是谁了
I don't know who I am anymore.
又要遛狗了啊
Walking dogs again?
嗯啊
Uh, yeah.
总要想办法挣那新手机呀
Gotta get that phone somehow.
再说在咕唧鸡的工作不太顺
And it beats working at kwikki chikki.
顺便说说  谢谢你啊
By the way, thanks.
谢啥呢
For what?
谢谢你故意演那么一出搞的被炒鱿鱼
For going all diva and getting fired on purpose.
对我意义很大
It meant a lot to me.
我不知道你在说啥呢
I don't know what you're talking about?
你难道不是故意发作起来为了帮我吗
Didn't you throw that tantrum just to help me?
那可不像我的作风啊
Doesn't sound like me.
好吧  随便你怎么演
Okay, well, however you want to play it,
我欠你个大人情
I owe you a solid.
拿着
Here.
这些基本都是大出来的
This is mostly solid.
哎呀  快瞧啊
Oh, look at that.
你的大哥大姐在叙兄妹情呢
Your brother and sister are sharing.
回来啦  你那"我和音乐"节目咋样
Hey, how was "Music and me"?
很好
Fine.
听着  下次能不能你带查莉去上课啊
Listen, could you take charlie to class next time?
以及之后的每一堂课都你去吧
And all the other times after that?
出什么事了
What happened?
有一点小误会
There was a little misunderstanding.
显然那个在"我和音乐"上出风头的人
Apparently the me in "Music and me"
不是我本人
Isn't me.
好啊  小查莉  是你大哥PJ
Hey, charlie. It's me, p.J.
我用泰迪的视频日记来告诉你这事
I'm taking over teddy's video diary to tell you that,
就算她其实不想承认
Even though she didn't want to admit it,
但是她今天还是为我做了好事
She did something really nice for me today.
我想有时候我们确实是彼此关心对方的
I guess sometimes we really do care about each other.
谁知道呢  也许这是一个全新的起点迈向
Who knows, maybe this is the start of a whole new...
PJ  你拿着我的摄录机干什么哪
P.J., what are you doing with my camera?!
我在跟查莉说话呀
- I'm talking to charlie.
还给我
Give me that.
才不  我还没讲完呢
No, I'm not done yet!
哼  你完了
Oh, yes you are.
有她这样的姐姐  祝你好运吧  查莉
With a sister like this, good luck, charlie.
哼  那是我要说的才对
Hey, I say that!
好运哦  小查莉
Good luck, charlie.
哦  好啊
Oh. Hi.
你好
Hello.
伊莲  我大概欠你个道歉
Look, elaine, I probably owe you an apology.
我是说  用唱儿歌来进行比赛的行为
I mean, making a competition out of Singing nursery rhymes,
实在太荒唐了
it's ridiculous.
不用道歉的  我也是很爱竞争的
No apology necessary. I can be very competitive.
信我吧  没人比我更爱争
Believe me, no one's more competitive than me.
我是在竞赛学校被选为最强竞赛选手的
I was voted most competitive at competition school.
您需要点什么
May I take your order? .
好的
Yes
我要点那三块鸡套餐
A three piece combo is what I'd like
再要给我的宝宝来个儿童餐
And a kid's meal for my little tyke
请给我六块鸡套餐
I will have your six piece platter
卷心菜或是土豆沙拉我不管
Slaw or potato salad it don't matter
再要特大号奶昔和薯条
Jumbo shake and a side of fries..
那我加上鸡腿一大桶
Might as well stick 'em on your meaty thighs